¬ Generated by localisation spreadsheet
{guild_recruit_merchant_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are sufficient merchants for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a merchant.
{guild_recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are enough of God's soldiers for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a priest. 
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are enough of God's servants for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a priest. 
{POPE_MISSION_SOURCE}The Dark Lord of Mordor
{COUNCIL_MISSION_SOURCE}Council of Nobles
{EXPLORERS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Explorers' Guild
{ASSASSINS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Assassins' Guild
{MERCHANTS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Merchants' Guild
{MASONS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Masons' Guild
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor has suffered enormously.
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor will suffer enormously. 
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor has suffered significantly.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor will suffer significantly.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor is not as high as it once was.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor will not be as high as it once was.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor has improved slightly.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor will improve slightly.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor has improved.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor will improve. 
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor has improved significantly.
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor will improve significantly.
{HUGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor has improved enormously.
{HUGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Dark Lord of Mordor will improve enormously. 
{VNV_ADORED_BY_POPE_DESCR}The Dark Lord of Mordor considers your leader one of his closest allies.
{VNV_ADORED_BY_POPE_PRE_DESCR}Your leader will become one of the Dark Lord's closest allies. 
{VNV_POPES_ENFORCER_DESCR}Your leader is the steel gauntlet of Dark Lord's will.
{VNV_POPES_ENFORCER_PRE_DESCR}Your leader will become the steel gauntlet of the Dark Lord's will.
{PLACE_OF_WORSHIP_REWARD_DESCR}The Masons' Guild has built you a place of worship.
{PLACE_OF_WORSHIP_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Masons' Guild have offered to construct place of worship for you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is thankful to you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be thankful to you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is impressed with you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be impressed with you.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_AVENGERS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_AVENGERS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_AVENGERS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_AVENGERS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild appreciates your efforts.
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild is far from impressed with your efforts.
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild will be not impressed with your efforts.
{FACTION_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}You have genuinely improved your relations with this faction.
{FACTION_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}You will improve your relations with this faction.
{FACTION_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}This faction thinks less of you.
{FACTION_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}You will disappoint this faction.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{blockade_heretic_TITLE}Blockade Port
{blockade_heretic_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to both punish these heretics and stop their unholy rot from spreading to the faithful.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_FAILURE}You have let down the Dark Lord of Mordor and the Almighty by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_heretic_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor and the Lord by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_pagan_TITLE}Blockade Port
{blockade_pagan_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to both punish these heathens and stop their unholy rot from spreading to the faithful.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has come to the fold, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_FAILURE}You have let down the Dark Lord of Mordor by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_pagan_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_islam_TITLE}Blockade Port
{blockade_islam_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to weaken these enemies of the Darkness.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has come to the fold, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_FAILURE}You have let down the Dark Lord of Mordor by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_islam_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor and the Lord by successfully blockading this port.
{city_small_church_TITLE}Build a Small Church
{city_small_church_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Dark Lord's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a Small Church in this city.
{city_small_church_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Small Church there.
{city_small_church_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; the Dark Lord of Mordor cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_small_church_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordors by failing to build a Small Church in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{city_small_church_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully building a Small Church in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{city_abbey_TITLE}Build an Abbey
{city_abbey_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Dark Lord of Mordor's attention that this settlement is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to build an Abbey in this settlement.
{city_abbey_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building an Abbey there.
{city_abbey_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; the Dark Lord of Mordor cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_abbey_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to build an Abbey in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{city_abbey_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully building an Abbey in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{city_cathedral_TITLE}Build a Cathedral
{city_cathedral_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Dark Lord of Mordor's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to build a Cathedral in this city.
{city_cathedral_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Cathedral there.
{city_cathedral_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; the Dark Lord of Mordor cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_cathedral_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to build a Cathedral in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{city_cathedral_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully building a Cathedral in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_TITLE}Build a Huge Cathedral
{city_huge_cathedral_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Dark Lord of Mordor's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to build a Huge Cathedral in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Huge Cathedral there.
{city_huge_cathedral_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; the Dark Lord of Mordor cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to build a Huge Cathedral in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully building a Huge Cathedral in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Lord in this city.
{castle_small_chapel_TITLE}Build a Small Chapel
{castle_small_chapel_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Dark Lord of Mordor's attention that this castle is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to build a Small Chapel in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this castle, you are no longer charged with building a Small Chapel there.
{castle_small_chapel_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; the Dark Lord of Mordor cares naught what you build in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to build a Small Chapel in this castle, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Lord in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully building a Small Chapel in this castle, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Lord in this castle.
{castle_chapel_TITLE}Build a Chapel
{castle_chapel_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Dark Lord of Mordor's attention that this castle is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to build a Chapel in this castle.
{castle_chapel_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this castle, you are no longer charged with building a Chapel there.
{castle_chapel_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; the Dark Lord of Mordor cares naught what you build in this castle.
{castle_chapel_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to build a Chapel in this castle, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Lord in this castle.
{castle_chapel_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully building a Chapel in this castle, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Lord in this castle.
{guild_recruit_spy_TITLE}Train Spy
{guild_recruit_spy_PROPOSAL}Sometimes a little bit of information is worth a dozen armies. The Guild requests that you train a Spy in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_spy_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Spy there.
{guild_recruit_spy_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Spy; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_spy_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Spy, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_merchant_TITLE}Train Merchant
{guild_recruit_merchant_PROPOSAL}Three things are required to make war and conquest; gold, gold and more gold. The Guild requests that you train a Merchant in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_merchant_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Merchant there.
{guild_recruit_merchant_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Merchant; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_merchant_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Merchant, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_priest_TITLE}Train Priest
{guild_recruit_priest_PROPOSAL}The Holy word requires another soldier of faith. The Guild requests that you train a Priest in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Priest there.
{guild_recruit_priest_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Priest; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_priest_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Priest, the Guild is very pleased.
{blockade_moderate_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{blockade_moderate_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 2 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{blockade_moderate_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{blockade_moderate_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{blockade_distant_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{blockade_distant_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 1 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{blockade_distant_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{blockade_distant_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{assassinate_captain_TITLE}Assassination Mission
{assassinate_captain_PROPOSAL}This miscreant's demise would please a great many people, not to mention make smoother our path to success. The Council suggests you send an assassin to hasten this man's journey into the next world. 
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your target has died; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This man has become our ally; it is no longer necessary to remove him.
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_HIDING}Your target has gone into hiding; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_captain_FAILURE}You have failed to assassinate this individual; the Council assumes this must be part of your great plan.
{assassinate_captain_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully assassinated this individual; the Council is impressed by your ruthlessness.
{steal_general_TITLE}A Proposal for the Princess's Hand
{steal_general_PROPOSAL}Lord %S has been beguiled by the lovely Princess %S. He is willing to pay a handsome dowry for her hand in marriage. The Council recommends you arrange this marriage as soon as possible.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_GENERAL_DEATH}Alas this marriage can never be, the general has died, and nearly left our Princess a widow.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_DEATH}Alas, the poor Princess has died; we must call the marriage off.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_TARGET_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, and this lord is twice such, he has married another. The marriage to our Princess is off.
{steal_general_FAILURE_PRINCESS_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, it seems our Princess has married another, the original marriage is off.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_RETIRED}Our Princess is now too old to marry; her time would be better spent on more solitary and contemplative pursuits. The marriage is off.
{steal_general_FAILURE}You have not arranged the marriage this Council recommended. The Council bows to your greater judgement in these matters.
{steal_general_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully arranged the marriage we recommended. This union is sure to bear fruit in time.
{join_crusade_TITLE}Join the invasion
{join_crusade_LEADER_TITLE}Your Leader must join the invasion.
{join_crusade_HEIR_TITLE}Your Heir must join the invasion.
{join_crusade_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor has called an invasion, and he has sent the call to arms to all devoted dark factions. You must create an invasion army within the time limit to take part.
{join_crusade_CHARACTER_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor has requested that %S demonstrate his loyalty and personally join the invasion.
{join_crusade_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor and proven your loyalty by successfully joining the invasion. 
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_FINISHED}The invasion has ended; you can no longer join. 
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_DEATH}Your General has died. As a result, you can no longer join the invasion.
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection. You have no place amongst the worthy; you can no longer join the invasion.
{join_crusade_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by not meeting your obligations to the Darkness and failing to join the invasion.
{return_papal_settlement_SUCCESS}You have greatly pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully returning Rome to The Papal States.
{return_papal_settlement_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to return Rome to The Papal States.
{return_papal_settlement_TITLE}Return Rome to the Papal States.
{return_papal_settlement_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor has requested that you return Rome to The Papal States. He will be greatly in your debt if you can see fit to return his home city.
{cease_hostilities_TITLE}Cease Hostilities
{cease_hostilities_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor demands that you stop shedding the blood of your fellow brothers. Cease hostilities against this faction immediately and do not carry out hostile acts for the duration of this mission.
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Dark Lord of Mordor is no longer concerned about the loyalty of this faction as it has been eliminated.
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection, Sauron no longer expects such as you to listen to the request of the Dark Lord.
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_TARGET_EXCOMMUNICATED}As this faction has lost Sauron's protection, it matters little how much of their unloyal blood you spill. You are no longer charged with ceasing hostilities with this faction.
{cease_hostilities_FAILURE}You have greatly saddened the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to cease hostilities with your fellow brothers, and continuing to shed the blood of your brother.
{cease_hostilities_SUCCESS}You have greatly pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by refraining from hostile actions against your fellow brothers. He only hopes this newfound peace will last.
{assassinate_cardinal_TITLE}Assassinate servant
{assassinate_cardinal_PROPOSAL}This servant's profanity and disrespect has deeply distressed the Dark Lord of Mordor. He assures you that he himself will smile upon you if you can deal with this delicate matter (kill him!).
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_DEATH}As this servant has died, the Dark Lord of Mordor has no need for you to 'deal' with him.
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}You have lost Sauron's protection, the Dark Lord no longer trusts you with this important duty.
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_HIDING}This servant cannot be found, the Dark Lord of Mordor has no need for you to 'deal' with him.
{assassinate_cardinal_FAILURE}The Dark Lord of Mordor is disquieted by your failure to 'deal' with this servant.
{assassinate_cardinal_SUCCESS}You have done Sauron a great favour, and much pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully assassinating this servant.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_TITLE}Assassinate the heretic
{assassinate_witch_heretic_PROPOSAL}This blasphemer is a stain in Sauron's eye and the he wishes you to cleanse it. Assassinate this person immediately!
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Dark Lord of Mordor has no need for you to assassinate this person, as they have perished.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; the Dark Lord does not trust the likes of you to uphold the way of the Darkness. You are no longer charged with the assassination of this person.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_HIDING}The Dark Lord of Mordor has no need for you to assassinate this person, as they cannot be found.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to assassinate this blasphemer as asked.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully assassinating this blasphemer, and thus making the world more pleasing to His eye.
{papal_blockade_port_TITLE}Blockade Port
{papal_blockade_port_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor only wishes that this prodigal son be returned to the fold. Perhaps cutting his income will make him see the darkness. Use your fleet to blockade this port for at least 3 turns.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_FAILURE}You have let down the Dark Lord of Mordor by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{papal_blockade_port_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor and the Lord by successfully blockading this port.
{break_alliance_TITLE}Break Alliance
{break_alliance_PROPOSAL}In uncertain times like these, it is important to know who one's true allies are. The Dark Lord of Mordor demands you break your alliance with this profane and heretical faction to prove your loyalty.
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_DEATH}As this faction has perished, you are no longer required to break your alliance with them.
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection. You are no longer required to break your alliance with this faction.
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer required to break your alliance with them.
{break_alliance_FAILURE}The Dark Lord of Mordor can only wonder what went wrong; you have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to break your alliance with this faction. 
{break_alliance_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor and proven your loyalty by successfully breaking your alliance with this faction.
{papal_build_church_TITLE}Build a Church
{papal_build_church_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Dark Lord of Mordor's attention that this settlement is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Dark Lord of Mordor wishes you to build a church in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, you are no longer charged with building a church there.
{papal_build_church_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection; The Dark Lord of Mordor cares naught what you build in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to build a church in this settlement, and thus hampering the proper worship of the Lord in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully building a church in this settlement, and thus propagating the proper worship of the Lord in this settlement.
{convert_TITLE}Spread the Word of the Lord
{convert_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor sees that the unbelievers in this settlement are clouding the judgement of the righteous. Send a priest to convert at least %d %% of the population to the darkness.
{convert_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your unloyal faction has lost Sauron's protection. One cannot expect a nest of vipers to bring forward the lambs. You are no longer charged with converting the people to the 'one true faith. 
{convert_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to convert sufficient people in this settlement.
{convert_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully spreading the word and bringing more lambs to His flock in this settlement.
{gift_from_pope_TITLE}A Gift from the Dark Lord of Mordor
{gift_from_pope_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor has noticed your loyalty and is pleased to grant you this gift.
{give_cash_TITLE}Give a "donation" to the Dark Lord of Mordor
{give_cash_PROPOSAL}The Lord favours he who is generous. Make a "donation" of at least %d florins to the Papal States. 
{give_cash_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor with your selfishness, by failing to "donate" sufficient florins to the Papal States.
{give_cash_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor with your generous "donation" to the Papal States. Blessed is he who gives.
{give_ancillary_TITLE}Give Relic to the Dark Lord of Mordor
{give_ancillary_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor has heard of your retrieval of this wondrous relic and sends his congratulations. You must hand over this relic to Sauron so that it may reside with him as is proper.
{give_ancillary_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by coveting this relic and thus failing to hand it over to Sauron.
{give_ancillary_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor sends you his gratitude for the rightful return of this relic to Sauron.
{recruit_priest_TITLE}Recruit a Priest
{recruit_priest_PROPOSAL}The dwindling number of dark-friends in this settlement reflects poorly on the Catholic Church. Recruit a priest in this settlement to convert more people.
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LOST}You have lost this settlement, you are no longer charged with recruiting a priest.
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your worthless faction has lost Sauron's protection, a priest from such a flock would be at best worthless. You are no longer charged with recruiting a priest.
{recruit_priest_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Dark Lord of Mordor by failing to recruit a priest, and thus hampering His Holy work.
{recruit_priest_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Dark Lord of Mordor by successfully recruiting a priest, and thus creating yet another vessel for His word.
{assassinate_general_TITLE}Assassination Mission
{assassinate_general_PROPOSAL}This miscreant's demise would please a great many people, not to mention make smoother our path to success. The Council suggests you send an assassin to hasten this man's journey into the next world. 
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your target has died; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This man has become our ally; it is no longer necessary to remove him.
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_HIDING}Your target has gone into hiding; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_general_FAILURE}You have failed to assassinate this individual; the Council assumes this must be part of your great plan.
{assassinate_general_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully assassinated this individual; the Council is impressed by your ruthlessness.
{council_blockade_port_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{council_blockade_port_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 3 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{council_blockade_port_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{council_blockade_port_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_TITLE}Take Rebel Settlement
{council_take_rebel_settlement_PROPOSAL}Our great nation appears weak to tolerate such insolence from these rebels. The Council recommends you capture this rebel settlement and assert your authority.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this Rebel settlement. You are no longer required to take it.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_FAILURE}It appears you have decided against this Council's advice by not taking this Rebel settlement, the Council can only assume this is yet another sudden turn in your labyrinth-like plan.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this Rebel settlement and displayed our strength to all.
{council_take_settlement_TITLE}Take Settlement
{council_take_settlement_PROPOSAL}It is time to further our great empire by extending our borders. The Council suggests you take this settlement for the glory of the nation.
{council_take_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this settlement.
{council_take_settlement_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to take it.
{council_take_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to take this settlement; perhaps you felt it was not the right time to expand our borders?
{council_take_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this settlement, and extended our Empire.
{guild_take_settlement_TITLE}Take Settlement
{guild_take_settlement_PROPOSAL}It is time to further our great empire by extending our borders. The Council suggests you take this settlement for the glory of the nation.
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this settlement.
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to take it.
{guild_take_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to take this settlement; perhaps you felt it was not the right time to expand our borders?
{guild_take_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this settlement, and extended our Empire.
{gift_from_council_TITLE}A Gift from the Council
{gift_from_council_PROPOSAL}The Council are greatly impressed by your leadership and would like you to accept this humble offering as a token of past and future endeavours.
{council_marry_princess_TITLE}A Proposal for the Princess's Hand
{council_marry_princess_PROPOSAL}Lord %S has been beguiled by the lovely Princess %S. He is willing to pay a handsome dowry for her hand in marriage. The Council recommends you arrange this marriage as soon as possible.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_GENERAL_DEATH}Alas this marriage can never be, the general has died, and nearly left our Princess a widow.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_DEATH}Alas, the poor Princess has died; we must call the marriage off.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_TARGET_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, and this lord is twice such, he has married another. The marriage to our Princess is off.
{council_marry_princess_FAILURE_PRINCESS_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, it seems our Princess has married another, the original marriage is off.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_RETIRED}Our Princess is now too old to marry; her time would be better spent on more solitary and contemplative pursuits. The marriage is off.
{council_marry_princess_FAILURE}You have not arranged the marriage this Council recommended. The Council bows to your greater judgement in these matters.
{council_marry_princess_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully arranged the marriage we recommended. This union is sure to bear fruit in time.
{annex_settlement_TITLE}Annex Settlement
{annex_settlement_PROPOSAL}By rights, this settlement should be under our authority. It is a mockery for it to be held by our rivals. The Council suggests you send a diplomat and attempt to have them to hand it over. You may be able to offer them a settlement that is less valuable to us in exchange.
{annex_settlement_EXPIRY_DEATH}The faction you were to treaty with has been vanquished. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to them. 
{annex_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another faction has taken this settlement. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to this faction.
{annex_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to convince our rivals to hand over this settlement; the Council is greatly disappointed at this turn of events.
{annex_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully convinced this faction to hand over land that is rightfully ours; the Council is much impressed by your obvious authority.
{send_emissary_TITLE}Send Emissary
{send_emissary_PROPOSAL}There are foreigners almost at our very gates and we know very little of them. The Council suggests you send an emissary to this faction and initiate diplomatic relations.
{send_emissary_EXPIRY_DEATH}The faction you were to meet with has been vanquished. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to them.
{send_emissary_FAILURE}You have failed to establish diplomatic relations with these people, the Council hopes this is for the best.
{send_emissary_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully established diplomatic relations with these people; the Council admires the ease with which you handle diplomacy.
{guild_take_settlement_TITLE}Take Settlement
{guild_take_settlement_PROPOSAL}The Guild's interests would be better looked after if this settlement were to become part of your empire. The Guild requests that you take this settlement.
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this settlement, the Guild no longer requires you to take it.
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_ALLIED}An alliance has been forged with this settlement, the Guild no longer requires you to take it.
{guild_take_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to take this settlement; the Guild is disappointed with this lack of progress.
{guild_take_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this settlement; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_recruit_agent_TITLE}Train Assassin
{guild_recruit_agent_PROPOSAL}Sometimes a single drop of poison or one knife in the dark can achieve what an entire army cannot. The Guild requests that you train an assassin in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_agent_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train an assassin there.
{guild_recruit_agent_FAILURE}You have failed to train an assassin; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_agent_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained an assassin, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_acquisition_TITLE}Mercantile Acquisition
{guild_acquisition_PROPOSAL}There is lucrative trade to be had here, but first we must deal with the opposition. The Guild recommends you send your merchant to make an acquisition of this merchants' trade. 
{guild_acquisition_EXPIRY_DEATH}It appears this merchant has perished; we no longer need to remove him.
{guild_acquisition_EXPIRY_HIDING}It appears this merchant has gone into hiding; we no longer need to remove him. 
{guild_acquisition_FAILURE}You have failed to complete the desired acquisition; the Guild is disappointed with this outcome. 
{guild_acquisition_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully made the acquisition; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_trade_agreement_TITLE}Obtain Trade Agreement
{guild_trade_agreement_PROPOSAL}We are losing lucrative trade opportunities, as we currently have no trade Agreement with this faction. The Guild would like you to obtain a trade agreement with these people.
{guild_trade_agreement_EXPIRY_DEATH}This faction has been vanquished; a trade agreement with them is no longer possible.
{guild_trade_agreement_EXPIRY_WAR}These fools have chosen war with us rather than peaceful trade. So be it, a trade agreement with them is no longer possible. 
{guild_trade_agreement_FAILURE}You have not obtained a trade agreement with this faction; the Guild is disappointed with this outcome.
{guild_trade_agreement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully obtained a Trade Agreement with this faction; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_build_TITLE}A Gift from the Mason's Guild
{guild_build_PROPOSAL}In recognition of your past aid and support to the Mason's Guild, the masons will build a place of worship in your honour, so that the faithful may gather.
{regicide_TITLE}Regicide
{regicide_PROPOSAL}My father is naught but a simpering fool. If left to rule he will bring only ruin to what should be my empire. Kill him so that I may lead my empire to greatness, and our empires will rule the world side by side as brothers. I am willing to generously 'recompense' you for your troubles.
{regicide_EXPIRY_DEATH}My 'noble' father has perished; you are no longer required to 'intervene'.
{regicide_EXPIRY_SOURCE_DEATH}The heir to this man's throne has passed away and you are no longer required to carry out his dark deeds. Of course, you wouldn't want your hard work to go to waste, and there's no harm in eliminating another rival.
{regicide_EXPIRY_HIDING}My father has gone to ground like the mole he is, you are no longer required to 'intervene'. 
{regicide_FAILURE}You have failed to deal with my wretched father as I requested, I will not forget this.
{regicide_SUCCESS}You have my endless gratitude; you have done both my people and myself a great favour. Your deed may go unsung but it will not go unrewarded, nor forgotten.
{crusade_active_TITLE}An invasion
{crusade_active_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor has called for an invasion to this settlement. It is time for righteous steel and arms strengthened by loyalty to free this part of dark land from his enemies.
{crusade_active_TARGET_PROPOSAL}It is a nightmarish day for your people that inhabit this settlement, for the Dark Lord of Mordor has called an invasion against it! The seemingly endless armies of the Darkness will soon be marching to lay siege to the walls... Make peace with the Dark Lord of Mordor, or make ready to defend it!
{jihad_active_TITLE}A Jihad
{jihad_active_PROPOSAL}A Jihad is moving on this settlement to clean away the infidels. It is time to dispense rightful anger upon these snakes in men's clothing.
{jihad_active_TARGET_PROPOSAL}A great Imam has called for the warriors of Islam to take up holy Jihad against your people and descend upon this settlement! The willingness of the Muslim soldiers' to die for such a cause make this one of the most terrifying perils the people of this place will ever face... Ensure they are prepared.
¬
{get_trait_PENALTY_DESCR}Your have lost an official title.
{get_trait_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your will lose any official titles.
{get_trait_REWARD_DESCR}The Dark Lord has bestowed an official title upon you.
{get_trait_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}You will gain an official title.
{get_trait_SOURCE}Trait Gain
{crusade_1a_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your treasury will benefit depending on number of victories.
{crusade_1a_SOURCE}Raid Called
{crusade_1b_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your treasury will benefit depending on number of victories.
{crusade_1b_SOURCE}Raid Called
{crusade_1a_EXPIRY_ALLIED}The Dark Lord of Mordor sees no benefit in attacking an allied faction, the Raid is called off.
{crusade_1a_EXPIRY_DEATH}How unfortunate for the general to die prematurely during the raid, you have lost a good opportunity to earn The Dark Lord's favour.
{crusade_1a_FAILURE}You failed The Dark Lord of Mordor, this will not go unpunished.
{crusade_1a_PROPOSAL}The more Men of Númenor you venquish, the better. Exterminating settlement's population is most welcome.
{crusade_1a_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor is pleased with the result of your warmongering campaign.
{crusade_1a_TITLE}Lead a Raid
{crusade_1b_EXPIRY_ALLIED}The Dark Lord of Mordor sees no benefit in attacking an allied faction, the Raid is called off.
{crusade_1b_EXPIRY_DEATH}How unfortunate for the general to die prematurely during the raid, you have lost a good opportunity to earn The Dark Lord's favour.
{crusade_1b_FAILURE}You failed The Dark Lord of Mordor, this will not go unpunished.
{crusade_1b_PROPOSAL}The more Men of the North you venquish, the better. Exterminating settlement's population is most welcome.
{crusade_1b_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor is pleased with the result of your warmongering campaign.
{crusade_1b_TITLE}Lead a Raid
{crusade_1c_EXPIRY_ALLIED}The Dark Lord of Mordor sees no benefit in attacking an allied faction, the Raid is called off.
{crusade_1c_EXPIRY_DEATH}How unfortunate for the general to die prematurely during the raid, you have lost a good opportunity to earn The Dark Lord's favour.
{crusade_1c_FAILURE}You failed The Dark Lord of Mordor, this will not go unpunished.
{crusade_1c_PROPOSAL}The more Elves you venquish, the better. Exterminating settlement's population is most welcome.
{crusade_1c_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor is pleased with the result of your warmongering campaign.
{crusade_1c_TITLE}Lead a Raid
{crusade_2a_EXPIRY_ALLIED}The Dark Lord of Mordor sees no benefit in attacking an allied faction, the Raid is called off.
{crusade_2a_EXPIRY_DEATH}How unfortunate for the general to die prematurely during the raid, you have lost a good opportunity to earn The Dark Lord's favour.
{crusade_2a_FAILURE}You failed The Dark Lord of Mordor, this will not go unpunished.
{crusade_2a_PROPOSAL}The more Men of Númenor you venquish, the better. Exterminating settlement's population is most welcome.
{crusade_2a_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor is pleased with the result of your warmongering campaign.
{crusade_2a_TITLE}Lead a Raid
{crusade_2b_EXPIRY_ALLIED}The Dark Lord of Mordor sees no benefit in attacking an allied faction, the Raid is called off.
{crusade_2b_EXPIRY_DEATH}How unfortunate for the general to die prematurely during the raid, you have lost a good opportunity to earn The Dark Lord's favour.
{crusade_2b_FAILURE}You failed The Dark Lord of Mordor, this will not go unpunished.
{crusade_2b_PROPOSAL}The more Men of the North you venquish, the better. Exterminating settlement's population is most welcome.
{crusade_2b_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor is pleased with the result of your warmongering campaign.
{crusade_2b_TITLE}Lead a Raid
{crusade_2c_EXPIRY_ALLIED}The Dark Lord of Mordor sees no benefit in attacking an allied faction, the Raid is called off.
{crusade_2c_EXPIRY_DEATH}How unfortunate for the general to die prematurely during the raid, you have lost a good opportunity to earn The Dark Lord's favour.
{crusade_2c_FAILURE}You failed The Dark Lord of Mordor, this will not go unpunished.
{crusade_2c_PROPOSAL}The more Elves you venquish, the better. Exterminating settlement's population is most welcome.
{crusade_2c_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor is pleased with the result of your warmongering campaign.
{crusade_2c_TITLE}Lead a Raid
{kill_crusader1_EXPIRY_ALLIED}Since there is no benefit in killing an ally, the mission is cancelled.
{kill_crusader1_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Council is disappointed to hear the target commander died without our intervention.
{kill_crusader1_EXPIRY_HIDING}The commander of The Dark Lord's armies has disappeared without a trace, there is no need to seek him anymore.
{kill_crusader1_FAILURE}The Council is disappointed with the news of your failure, so is all righteous folk.
{kill_crusader1_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor is gathering forces to strike nearby lands, destroy his army and its leader.
{kill_crusader1_SUCCESS}The Council has established that the target character was eliminated.
{kill_crusader1_TITLE}Kill the commander of gathering invasion forces.
{kill_crusader2_EXPIRY_ALLIED}Since there is no benefit in killing an ally, the mission is cancelled.
{kill_crusader2_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Council is disappointed to hear the target commander died without our intervention.
{kill_crusader2_EXPIRY_HIDING}The commander of The Dark Lord's armies has disappeared without a trace, there is no need to seek him anymore.
{kill_crusader2_FAILURE}The Council is disappointed with the news of your failure, so is all righteous folk.
{kill_crusader2_PROPOSAL}The Dark Lord of Mordor is gathering forces to strike nearby lands, destroy his army and its leader.
{kill_crusader2_SUCCESS}The Council has established that the target character was eliminated.
{kill_crusader2_TITLE}Kill the commander of gathering invasion forces.

¬##### Script: One Ring
{destroyOneRing_TITLE}The path to Mount Doom is clear!
{destroyOneRing_PROPOSAL}You can destroy the One Ring. Press "Accept" to destroy it now. Press "Decline" if you want to delay.
{destroyOneRing_FAILURE}As you wish.
{giveRingSauron_TITLE}Give the One Ring to Sauron
{giveRingSauron_PROPOSAL}You can now give the One Ring to Sauron. Press "Accept" to do it; press "Decline" if for whatever reason you want to delay the transfer.
{giveRingSauron_SUCCESS}The Dark Lord of Mordor sends you his gratitude for the rightful delivery of the One Ring. Master Sauron is back and he is most pleased by your effort!
{giveRingSauron_FAILURE}Sauron can wait, but not for too long...
{keep_ring_TITLE}Keep the One Ring for ourselves?
{keep_ring_PROPOSAL}The forests around Isengard have fallen silent, the animals scamper to their homes as they behold the power in your hands. Now that the One Ring is secured, our Lord Saruman may wear it and wield it.
{keep_ring_SUCCESS}The power of the One Ring in the hands of Lord Saruman will soon give us the ability to recruit Nazg-hai.
{keep_ring_FAILURE}A wise decision, my Lord.
{ring_choice_FAILURE}For your noble quest, you received 10000 coins in cash and your king's purse will be increase by 500 coins. In order to destroy the One Ring, move the ringbearer into the region of Barad-dûr and stay there until you'll find a way to throw it into the the fiery chasm of Mount Doom whence it came from!
{ring_choice_PROPOSAL}Carrying the Ring is a heavy task. On the other hand, you are the only capable to destroy it.\n-Press "Accept" if you wish to relinquish the One Ring and let us hide it.\n-Press "Decline" if you believe you can take the Ring deep into Mordor and cast it back into Mount Doom to destroy it!
{RING_CHOICE_PAYBACK_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}If you press "Decline", you 'll receive several resources from the Council to aid you in your quest and the gratitude of all "good" factions.
{RING_CHOICE_PAYBACK_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}If you press "Accept", there would be a small diplomatic penalty with every "good" faction. But you'll get rid of that cursed ring.
{ring_choice_SUCCESS}The One Ring was removed from our ringbearer and now it is lost again.
{ring_choice_TITLE}White Council's dilemma
{WHITECOUNCIL_MISSION_SOURCE}The White Council
